$SS_INSTALLSSTRIPDONE_NOTIFY	SerialStrip installed.
$SS_TIMEBETWEENANIMANDSTRIP	Time between anim & strip
$SS_TIMEBETWEENANIMANDSTRIP_DESC	After a stripping animation ends, this defines how long to wait until the items are stripped\nAdjust according to your system's speed to achieve best results.
$SS_UNINSTALLSSTRIP	Uninstall SerialStrip
$SS_UNINSTALLSSTRIP_DESC	This will remove any values and arrays that SerialStrip may have created, so that it can be uninstalled safely without leaving trash in the savegame.\nAfter this, save the game and remove the mod.
$SS_UNINSTALLSSTRIPCONFIRM_MSG	This will uninstall SerialStrip.\nProceed?
$SS_UNINSTALLSSTRIPDONE_MSG	SerialStrip has been uninstalled. Please save your game and remove the mod.